<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>09 ====== END ======</name>
	<author>GlowingBear0696</author>
	<url>https://github.com/GlowingBear0696/LotR_LO</url>
	<supportedVersions><li>1.0</li></supportedVersions>
	<description>&lt;color=yellow&gt;&lt;size=24&gt;What goes below this load order divider:&lt;/size&gt;&lt;/color&gt;

&lt;color=green&gt;This is just a placeholder for the END&lt;/color&gt;


&lt;color=yellow&gt;&lt;size=24&gt;Contributors&lt;/size&gt;&lt;/color&gt;

Trisscar: For this wonderful load order guide and inspiration.


&lt;color=yellow&gt;========================
&lt;size=24&gt;Changelog&lt;/size&gt;
========================&lt;/color&gt;
1.0.1 (11-09-2018)
========================
Updated to v4 of Trisscar's Load Order Guide.

1.0.0 (10-29-2018)
========================
Initial release for RimWorld 1.0



&lt;color=yellow&gt;================================================
Full Guide (below here) -- Courtesy of Trisscar on Discord
================================================&lt;/color&gt;

Mod Order Guide V4
Credit-'Chevalier XLIV' for readable format, as opposed to previous wall-of-text eye bleeding.

&lt;color=green&gt;-Core:&lt;/color&gt;
Core
Hugslib
Jecstools
Humanoid
!Prepare Carefully! - &lt;i&gt;Either here, or bottom of the mod list, occasional weird issues.&lt;/i&gt;

Libraries - &lt;i&gt;Core file packets, if something says it has no content, just code for other mods to build from, that's a library.&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Terra Core goes here.&lt;/i&gt;

THEN

&lt;i&gt;immediately after libraries&lt;/i&gt;
Giddy-up Core
Giddy-up Addons
Exp. Doors
Third Age
&lt;i&gt;If running Combat Extended, it is theorized that it should go right above Third Age, patch to both goes right below both.&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;i&gt;In theory Rimworld of Magic goes here.&lt;/i&gt;

AFTER ALL OF THAT

&lt;color=green&gt;-Map Generation:&lt;/color&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Anything that adds biomes, messes with how maps work, or changes how the world map generates. Grand Rivers and Archipelagos go here.&lt;/i&gt;

&lt;color=green&gt;-Factions:&lt;/color&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Anything that ONLY adds new factions, not new races or types of pawns. Faction Control goes here.&lt;/i&gt;

&lt;color=green&gt;-Trait Mods:&lt;/color&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Rainbeau's made a few of these. If it just adds traits, or adds slots, it goes here.&lt;/i&gt;

&lt;color=green&gt;-Medical Mods:&lt;/color&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Yes this includes those that add new bionic parts. No it does not include mods that ONLY add medical items. EPOE and Rah's and A Dog Said and Archotech are examples of medical mods.&lt;/i&gt;

&lt;color=green&gt;-Game Behavior:&lt;/color&gt;
&lt;i&gt;While You're Up/Hand Me That Brick go here, but ALSO mods like Steel Isn't Flammable, Fewer Inferno Cannons and Greenworld, anything that changes how pawns, items, buildings, or events behave. Emphasis on GAME behaviour.&lt;/i&gt;

&lt;color=green&gt;-Items:&lt;/color&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Clothing, hair, buildings, items; hats, weapons, Vegetable Garden, nuclear power plants, Rimfactory, Climate Control and Advanced Bridges.&lt;/i&gt;

&lt;color=green&gt;-Races (and new animals):&lt;/color&gt;
!!RACES GO AT THE BOTTOM THIS IS NOT A DRILL!!
&lt;i&gt;Includes Animal Collab, Arachnophobia, Werewolves, Vampires, and other mods that make massive changes to pawns just by being loaded.&lt;/i&gt;


&lt;i&gt;Sometimes two mods will conflict, and might be fixed by putting one of them above the other when it otherwise wouldn't be. Try this if you have done everything else here and the error still occurs.&lt;/i&gt;


	</description>
</ModMetaData>
